http://www.coastphoto.com/index.php/privacy-policy

Request for Quote
EventsGroup PortraitureDocumentation & AwardsPortrait StudioIn-Box Photo BoothGreen ScreenActivities & EntertainmentDecor & SetsPhoto Hikes and WalksTeam BuildingGolf TournamentsSporting EventsSlideshows & VideosOutbound with CMPHoliday FestivitiesGreat GiftsCommercialArchitectural ExteriorsArchitectural InteriorsExecutive PortraitsFood & BeveragePublic RelationsEditorialAerialTour & TravelIndustrial & ConstructionRental PropertiesPromo VideoTear SheetsWeddingsWedding PhotographyEngagement SessionsIn-Box Photo BoothWedding VideographyPortraits & ActionFamily PortraitsSnow & Bike ActionSnow & Bike VideosBike Park PhotosWhistler Kids ProgramOn Whistler/BlackcombSliding Center PhotosStockStock Image LibraryTimelapse FootageAbout UsWho We AreOur BlogJobs & EmploymentIn The CommunityOwnersOur GalleryBook UsContact Us
What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: ; To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs); To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
; To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.Do we use cookies? We do not use cookies.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. www.coastphoto.com105-4122 Village GreenWhistler, BC V0N1B4CanadaThis email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
back to top
Coast Mountain Photography © 2020 • Privacy Policy
Blog Categories
Event PhotographyCommercial PhotographyWedding PhotographyStock PhotographyPortrait & Action Photography
